thefinancialword.com 2018-01-27

# Privacy and Cookies Policy - TheFinancialWord

**PRIVACY POLICY**

** ** Your privacy is important to Bulletpoint Digital.  This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that Bulletpoint Digital collects, and the ways in which Bulletpoint Digital uses that personal information.

**Personal information collection**

This website does not support “Do Not Track” requests. Bulletpoint Digital, by itself or through third parties, may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

  * information about your use of this website (including the IP addresses, or domain names of users, uniform resource identifier, time of request, country of origin, browser and operating system used, time spent on site and time spent on pages within the site);
  * information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the website (including First Name, Last Name, Email Address, Postal Address);
  * information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services (including First Name, Last Name, Email Address, Postal Address); and
  * any other information that you send to Bulletpoint Digital.

**Using personal information**

Bulletpoint Digital may use your personal information to:

  * administer this website;
  * personalize the website for you;
  * enable your access to and use of the website services;
  * publish information about you on the website;
  * send to you products that you purchase;
  * supply to you services that you purchase;
  * send you marketing communications.

Where Bulletpoint Digital discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, Bulletpoint Digital may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

**Securing your data**

Bulletpoint Digital will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

Bulletpoint Digital will store all the personal information you provide.

**Cross-border data transfers**

Information that Bulletpoint Digital collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which Bulletpoint Digital operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available around the world.

You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

**Updating this statement**

Bulletpoint Digital may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.

You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

**Other websites**

This website contains links to other websites.

Bulletpoint Digital is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

**Contact Bulletpoint Digital**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or Bulletpoint Digital’s treatment of your personal information, please write:

  * by email to contact@thefinancialword.com; or
  * by post to 2885 Sanford Ave SW #31899, Grandville, MI 49418.

**Credit**

This document was created using a Contractology template available at [http://www.freenetlaw.com](http://www.freenetlaw.com/).

* * *

**COOKIES POLICY**

**About cookies**

This website uses cookies.  By using this website and agreeing to this policy, you consent to Bulletpoint Digital’s use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy.

Cookies are files sent by web servers to web browsers, and stored by the web browsers.

The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server.  This enables a web server to identify and track web browsers.

There are two main kinds of cookies: session cookies and persistent cookies.  Session cookies are deleted from your computer when you close your browser, whereas persistent cookies remain stored on your computer until deleted, or until they reach their expiry date.

**Cookies on our website**

Bulletpoint Digital uses the following cookies on this website, for the purposes of identifying users, tracking actions, remembering preferences, serving advertisements and messages, remarketing users with advertisements and messages, enabling interaction with third party social networks and sharing platforms, and other purposes more specifically detailed below.

**Google cookies**

Bulletpoint Digital uses Google Analytics to analyze the use of this website.  Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users’ computers.  The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store and use this information.  Google’s privacy policy is available at: http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html.

Bulletpoint Digital publishes Google Adsense interest-based advertisements on this website.  These are tailored by Google to reflect your interests.  To determine your interests, Google will track your behavior across the web using cookies and will use that data to serve you ads/messages on sites across the web.  You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser using Google’s Ads Preference Manager, available at: http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/.  You can opt-out of the Adsense partner network cookie at: http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html.  However, this opt-out mechanism uses a cookie, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained. To ensure that an opt-out is maintained in respect of a particular browser, you should use the Google browser plug-in available at: http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/plugin.

**Other third party cookies**

When you use this website, you may also be sent the following third party cookies, which may be used for the following purposes:

  * Adblade (Adblade.com/Congoo LLC) collects cookie and usage data and may use information collected about you to serve ads and messages customized to your behavior and interests.
  * Bing Ads (Microsoft Corporation) collects cookie and usage data and may use information collected about you to serve ads and messages customized to your behavior and interests.
  * Taboola Monetize Content (Taboola Inc.) collects cookie and usage data and may use information collected about you to serve ads and messages customized to your behavior and interests.
  * Google AdWords conversion tracking (Google) is a service that collects cookie and usage data for purposes of tracking actions performed on this site.
  * Google Analytics remarketing and similar audiences features in Adwords (Google) are services that use cookie and usage data to connect activity on this site with the Adwords and Doubleclick advertising networks. The collected information enables Google and its partners (including Bulletpoint Digital), to serve advertising based on your activity.
  * Google+ +1 button and social widgets (Google) are services that collect cookie and usage data and enable interaction with the Google+ social network.
  * Facebook Ads conversion tracking (Facebook) is a service that collects cookie and usage data for purposes of tracking actions performed on this site.
  * Facebook Comments (Facebook) is a service that collects cookie and usage data and enables users to leave and share comments on the Facebook platform. If email address is provided by the user, it may be used to send notifications of comments made in the discussion.
  * Facebook Like button and social widgets (Facebook) are services that collect cookie and usage data and enable interaction with the Facebook social network.
  * Facebook Remarketing (Facebook) is a service that uses cookie and usage data to connect activity on this site with the Facebook advertising network. The collected information enables Facebook and its partners (including Bulletpoint Digital), to serve advertising based on your activity.
  * Twitter Tweet button and social widgets (Twitter) are services that collect cookie and usage data and enable interaction with the Twitter social network.
  * Pinterest “Pin it” button and social widgets (Pinterest) are services that collect cookie and usage data and enable interaction with the Pinterest platform.

You may opt out of the use of cookies by other third parties by visiting <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/#completed>. This opt-out mechanism uses a cookie, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained.  You should visit this page periodically to review your preferences, or update to include new participating companies.

**Refusing cookies**

Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies.

In Internet Explorer, you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector.

In Firefox, you can adjust your cookies settings by clicking “Tools”, “Options” and “Privacy”.

Blocking cookies will have a negative impact upon the usability of some websites.

**Credit**

This document was created using a Contractology template available at [http://www.freenetlaw.com](http://www.freenetlaw.com/).
